# **MARK NOU**



619-850-4181

mark.nou7@gmail.com



San Diego, CA 92105

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Recent graduate from California State University San Marcos with a BA in Environmental Studies. Dedicated professional with 5 years of proven performance in management, leadership, recruiting, and team building. Detail-oriented in finances, planning, and analytics. Ready to make an immediate contribution to your organization.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### GENERAL MANAGER, San Diego, CA

Sunshine Industries Inc - Logistics Contractor, June 2021-Present

- Start up multiple contracts with partners Global Logistics Systems and Ontrac. Manage two sites and worked hand in hand with warehouse management and operations.
- Review and oversee all inbound and outbound invoices and payments, finances, and profit and losses.
- Gather, analyze, and report on finances, budgets, and company performance on a monthly basis. Implement budgeting and operations plans to mitigate loses and increase efficiency.
- Oversee a team of 40 employees ensuring efficient operations and quality service. Responsible for hiring, onboarding, and reviewing employee performance.
- Direct inbound and outbound transportation operations, warehouse activities, safety performance, and logistics quality management.

#### **OPERATIONS MANAGER, San Diego, CA**

Sublime Express - Amazon DSP, April 2019-June 2021

- Manage company operations with responsibility for profit and loss. Organize and execute scheduling, training and inventory control
- Improve morale and management communication by creating employee recognition and rewards practices.
- Create interview questionnaires, job descriptions and advertisements, pre-screening protocols, and post-interview assessments.
- Hired, onboarded, and trained over 300 employees for full time positions as well as for Peak seasons.

## WAREHOUSE ASSISTANT, San Diego, US

Foresight Sports, Of America, May 2018-April 2019

- Conduct timely and accurate inventory counts to maintain current supply records and facilitate smooth ordering
- Consult item numbers and storage locations to stock warehouse quickly and efficiently.

#### LEAD DELIVERY DRIVER, San Diego, CA

Regents Pizzeria, May 2015-March 2019

- Deliver food in timely manner to customers in La Jolla, San Diego.
- Take food orders and served food inhouse with exceptional customer service.
- Train new drivers and employees on expected standards and duties.

• Prepare ingredients and cooked meals according to established recipes.

# LANDSCAPE LABORER, San Diego, US

Dao Landscaping, Of America, June 2013-May 2015

- Operate and maintain basic landscaping equipment and vehicles
- Install irrigation systems, fence installations, and pavement.

# **EDUCATION**

## BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ENVIRONMENTAL STUDIES, San Marcos, CA

California State University, May 2021

# ASSOCIATE IN ARTS (A.A.) IN ENVIRONMENTAL STUDIES, Oceanside, CA

MiraCosta College, June 2019

## **SKILLS**

Performance Management		Workforce Management		Multi-Unit Operations Managemen			Microsoft Excel	
Microsoft Office	Leadership	p Teamwork	Problem-Solving		Adaptability	Strong Math Skills		